bt24news.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | bt24News

### Privacy Polivy

**http://www.bt24news.com/ respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you give to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or people outside of http://www.bt24news.com/.

**Credit card details**

http://www.bt24news.com/ will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on http://www.bt24news.com/.

**External Sites.**

http://www.bt24news.com/ is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows http://www.bt24news.com/ to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and http://www.bt24news.com/ does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you send to http://www.bt24news.com/ and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through http://www.bt24news.com/ have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:biztechcitadel@gmail.com)
